Hello hello everyone welcome back to my channel
keep creating friends in today's first video
we did weekly market highlights
see all the important news and indicators the central government has told the Supreme Court
that it will
itself refund the interest of the moratorium period on all the people below 2 crores, so it is possible
that many people can benefit from this
so due to this news there can be a
lot of hustle and bustle in the banking sector and especially the public sector banks
in the coming few days and we will have to see
how the market reacts to the decision of the center in the
next few days keeping all these news and
indicators in mind which
fundamentals should you
consider for investing
and at which valuation level
you can buy them, we will discuss that in this video
before starting the video let me
tell you that if you have not yet subscribed to the channel then
this matching love you
to information and ideas about
interest and wealth  Your
subscriptions, likes and comments motivate me even more
and I keep
pushing you to create videos from this, so don't forget to click the like button,
subscribe to the channel and also to get notifications, so that you do
n't miss any of the upcoming videos. You
can also follow us on Facebook, Twitter and Telegram so
that you can increase your knowledge. The links are
given in the description. So without further ado, let's get
started friends,
today our first chapter is related to the banking sector
and that is India's best bank,
India's best private bank, All India
Congress Bank. Over all, that is HDFC
Bank. We have done an in-depth
analysis of HDFC Bank in that video, in which
we saw many of its fundamental
attributes, saw the metrics, saw the
written test,
gave its tutorial performance and including its theft, it has been
conscious, fundamentals, strong talk and such a
consistent performance over the last decade,
we discussed it in detail. I will add the link of that video to add
now this
video to that link.  You can check it further. If we
talk about HDFC Bank share market capitalization, then its mark-up is around six lakh crores. It is the
largest bank in India. In
terms of market capitalization, dividend
yield point should be in front. Talk about it in the first 15th of
all the videos and the details of that.
RBI has put a regulation on the bank that to
preserve its gas, it should
not post any tweet to its market right now.
Due to this regulation, you might be
seeing less of it, but that temple
is a mode of situation. I think that in the
future, its demand is going to be good. It is going to be
a very David
Scott type of a very requested group.
So I do not think that it will
take a dip. It is going to remain at this low level going
forward. The meter's value is 1.06. So, for those who are
new to our channel and are watching our videos for the
first time, let me
tell you that when the price is below the value of the stock,
we believe that that particular
stock is trading lower than the overall market
and in the past  It is more than 54, as we
saw here, 1.06, which means that the
stock has a higher volatility than the market. So, for
financial sector stocks, you will
find that in the reverse, finance stocks have a
beta greater than 1 in the last week, which is why they have a
higher volatility than the market.
Whereas, stocks like pharma and
defense sector stocks have
lower volatility. So, HDFC
Bank's beta 1.0 is just a little bit harder than the market.
You can
get it at a slight discount to the industry peers. But keep it up. So, such a
great, such a great
stock is
available at a discount to the industry peers. It has a good,
very respectable delivery percentage of 14%.
Now, if we talk about its first set,
if you get SDFC Bank stock somewhere
between 1000 and 1050, that is, 1000 and 2050, then it can be
a good, respectable
level. For long term
investment, if you have some patience in it.
Tulsi Yadav wants to wait a bit, banking data of birth light of
the recent developments from the Central
Government and Supreme Court. So,
you want to see those earrings, you
want to wait and see that this situation becomes a little
clearer, then I will invest. So
if you
want to wait a little in this, and if
its quality comes a little in the market, because when
friends design and development of material,
external research, then if you get this stock
between 750 and 300, then this can be a
very good level for long term
investment. HDFC Bank has a
large staff, which you should
definitely set your investment target low.
Our other staff is also
appointed medical staff from the banking sector. Welcome One does
not do equally valuable banquets. Its
capital operation strategy is very
important, it has a lot of risk cover. And
right now this is such a time that
in time to survive, so whatever banks subscribe,
you will also do it in the future. So, I see Kotak
Mahindra Bank as a very good play for the future.
Kotak Mahindra Bank's
market employees have invested around 2.5 lakh crores
in this.  They haven't even done AB
as they
saw with the previous bank. As per bank regulations, the
bank has not yet done any one but its
beta is also 1.08, so the
tile is slightly higher than the market. Inducted
around 125 and this gives you a good prevention
on the back of Jaipur. So they charge
you a little premium for good stops.
However, that is not the case with HDFC Bank.
It is a bit of an option.
Despite being a champion, it has such a
good Welcome Untied Fund. Despite this,
you get a little discount on the back of the industry.
But here is the question. At a
slight pigmentation of 4, it is
getting in comparison to the industry's PK. The
respectable delivery percentage of 3738 percent
is a good 12%. Talking about its price off,
if you get this track
somewhere between 12 and a half to 13, then this could be a good level for
investing in a different flavor.
If you want to invest in Kotak Mahindra Bank
for the long term, then it could be
a good level for that. But if you
want to wait a little in the market
Volatility remains a bit in the near term,
so if you get this trick at the level of 11 to 1150,
which is the support of which you
can see that when it fell in March, it had given so much
support between 1150 and 1150, so that is a good
price, it can be for long term
investment, if you
want to invest in Kotak Mahindra Bank, then
I think this bank should be
in your investment portfolio like HDFC Bank because its
fundamentals are very low, such alarm,
but in the general insurance sector, the
market leader of private players is
Aman Paudhe, private players in the general
insurance sector, the market application of this company is
around 600 crores, the
difference is a bit low, point to point, as
I have seen, financial stocks have to be done
at a higher difference now, so its delivery from this is
12.27 which is a bit low,
even within the financial sector, we have
discussed this in many of the earlier videos that
even in the finance sector, such stocks like those which are
not from the life insurance sector, then from the general insurance sector  If they are,
their beta is a little lower.
Described in the Dubai
financial sector, their beta is a little lower
because they are slightly lower than the market.
Life insurance general elections
practice time, so its beta
is the industry's appointment. This is 2010 and you are getting a small
premium calculation for 6%.
But because it is a private sector
channel statement from a leading market
player, its premium
valuation is a little justified. A
very strong delivery
percentage of 67 percent, so this shows
how much confidence investors have in it. People are taking delivery of it by filling it in their
long-term investment accounts. If we
talk about its district level house price chart, then if you find it anywhere between 1250 and 13, then
it can be a good
different level. Now I can see that it has
tried to take support at this level many times, so a very good support level is
550 to 1323. If you want to wait a little,
and due to near-term quality, this shop,
if you  If it is available between 11 to 1150 then it can be a
very great red. It is a
very good shot for long term investment. It is a
company with good fundamentals.
Hello friends, this is the uncrowned king of this chapter.
Our next office Hindustan Unilever.
Whatever I say about this company will be
less. It is the market leader
in many segments and the two most popular fronts,
so with the most positive perspectives.
Hindustan Unilever's market
capitalization in India is around Rs 5 lakh crore, around Rs
4 lakh 90 thousand crore. The search is quite
good. There is an increase of 6 percent on point in many reports.
Son, its points are so
as I talked about earlier, it is a
stock of FD sector, so it is much lower than the market.
Which you can
see here in the media bag, the base of the industry,
Dixit and you are
getting it at less than that, but on the back of Family Two.
On Railways, St. Petersburg 1234 percent clothes
decently percentage, this stop if you want to invest between 2000 to
2050  If you get it between then it can be a very good
level, it is a very powerful stock,
very calm fundamentals, very high
return on equity fund companies, best
free company, companies with positive test for
long term, it may be good to
invest in, if
you get it at the level of 2000 to 2050,
but if you
want to wait a little and you get this stock
at the level of 1950 to 2000, then it may be
even better, your
marksheet will increase even more,
our Play Store's related to housing finance
sector, that HDFC Limited, which is the
market leader in the housing finance sector, the
company with the highest sales and most buildings
is in the housing finance sector, HDFC Limited, which is the
parent company of many other strike
companies like HDFC Bank, HDFC
Life, etc. and its 12 unlimited net
use, and I want to say that it is a very
good group and this is the parent company
of that group, SDMC Limited's
market capitalization is around three lakh 22
thousand crores, delivery is quite
Respectably, the remaining 1.17% is quite
active, its rate is 1.24, so
this embassy is a housing finance
company, so its rate is a little higher than the
market, so the
order telescope is the base of the industry,
and you are getting this on its compass, a little
prevention on the back of ATM,
then you are getting this pimpl valuation, according to the
back of the industry, the delivery
percentage is very impressive, let's go
on a good delivery of 50%,
this shows how much faith there is in HDFC Limited
and it has been such a big wealth
creation group for India
that it is no surprise that a lot of people have put it
on the install,
if you find HDFC Limited stock
anywhere between 1704, then it can be very good
for long term investment, if you want to wait a little and
if you see some quality in the market,
you are coming in, then 1516 sugar
level can be an even better level if you are a
long term investor  If we
consider HDFC Limited, then our
last stock today is Bajaj Finserv. Bajaj Finserv
Paint Companies, Bajaj Finance, Bajaj Allianz
General Insurance, Life Insurance. Currently, the
market value of the company Simple Companies Bajaj Finserv is
around Rs 96,000 crore (approximately Rs 1 lakh crore). The dividend is quite
low because it is a growth-oriented stock.
We have seen that the stocks of the financial sector are
not doing much different,
so the dividend history is
looking quite low. You can see the points of Rohit's
daughters, its 1.35. So, out of all the stocks
you look at, the highest quality one is seen
in Christopher. Of these,
this is Twenty Nine and you are getting it at a very
expensive elevation of 144, quite free
valuation. So, you can put some weight on this topic. The
delivery percentage which we can also see here
is less than the delivery percentage of the top, so
you can put some weight on this price level. A
little below this price, when Stark comes,
you can mix it in. My
opinion is that this  If you
get the stock between 6000 and 6000 from childhood, then this may be a raw
level, but if you want to wait a little,
and because we have seen that this
time is a little more than the start marvel market, then if the market comes to ₹1, then during
this time you can definitely see the quality
and in such a situation, if this trick
gives you the same feature from 4000 to 45, then it can be a
very good one, in that the
margin objective of A will increase well and then the
staff will invest and this
trick, I think, has a
very good potential for the long term, as
we saw that the Government of India
tried to cover the launch up to 22 crores, in which there are
consumer finance companies, housing
finance companies,
so it can benefit
companies like HDFC Limited, Bajaj Finserv, which are
in consumer finance and housing finance, and the best and most prolific Bank
of India, HDFC Bank, Kotak
Mahindra Bank, then they can benefit
because the companies with the best fundamentals will
benefit the most if
in the finance sector  If there is any consolidation
and whatever relief is given by the government, then the
company with transfer number will benefit the most from this, now we have discussed the
tractor in this video, friends, today's
video will give you clear knowledge through this, the
mission of this channel is to reach you immediately
and in every upcoming video we will
discuss many interesting topics
and I will have user ID or hot
office avatar for you, similarly every weekend we will keep sharing
weekly market updates and our views about the
current situation, so
definitely subscribe to the channel and
events were posted earlier, if
you like pornographic video updates then
like the video, if you think that this information can be
helpful then share it with your friends and
family members and
subscribe to the channel, we will meet you in the next video
with notification, till then take
care of these things